<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.11</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>RoboSoft 4.0.756</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>https://robosoft.rudenko.com</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used
      by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software
      products. To find out more go to https://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
  <RoboSoft>
    <Company_UIN>CMP-00551AFE9C7</Company_UIN>
    <Company_Description>KARPOLAN is a nickname of Anton Karpenko</Company_Description>
    <Product_UIN>APP-009B0227604</Product_UIN>
    <Search_String>Auto Mute</Search_String>
    <Press_Release_Search_String>Auto Mute</Press_Release_Search_String>
    <NewsFeed_Search_String>Auto Mute</NewsFeed_Search_String>
    <Search_Engine_Search_String>Auto Mute</Search_Engine_Search_String>
    <Web_Directories_Search_String>Auto Mute</Web_Directories_Search_String>
    <Search_String_Unique>KARPOLAN</Search_String_Unique>
    <Comments_For_Reviewer>Thank you for your interest. Hope this program helps you too :)</Comments_For_Reviewer>
    <Publish_on_CD>TRUE</Publish_on_CD>
    <Backlink>https://auto-mute.com/submit.html</Backlink>
    <RSProductType></RSProductType>
  </RoboSoft>
  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>KARPOLAN</Company_Name>
    <Address_1>#101 - 1001 W. Broadway, 381</Address_1>
    <Address_2></Address_2>
    <City_Town>Vancouver</City_Town>
    <State_Province>BC</State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code>V6H 4E4</Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country>Canada</Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>https://karpolan.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Contact_First_Name>Anton</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Karpenko</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Contact_Email>
      <Author_First_Name>Anton</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Karpenko</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Author_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>pad@karpolan.com</General_Email>
      <Sales_Phone>38 093 3944815</Sales_Phone>
      <Support_Phone>38 093 3944815</Support_Phone>
      <General_Phone>38 093 3944815</General_Phone>
      <Fax_Phone>38 093 3944815</Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
  </Company_Info>
  <ASP>
    <ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
    <ASP_Member>Y</ASP_Member>
    <ASP_Member_Number>04242</ASP_Member_Number>
  </ASP>
  <NewsFeed>
    <NewsFeed_FORM>Y</NewsFeed_FORM>
    <NewsFeed_VERSION>1.0</NewsFeed_VERSION>
    <NewsFeed_URL>https://Submit-Everywhere.com/extensions/NewsFeed.htm</NewsFeed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Type>Atom 1.0</NewsFeed_Type>
    <NewsFeed_Language>English</NewsFeed_Language>
    <NewsFeed_Purpose>News</NewsFeed_Purpose>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Email>pad@karpolan.com</NewsFeed_Author_Email>
    <NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>Anton</NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>Karpenko</NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Feed_URL>https://auto-mute.com/feed/</NewsFeed_Feed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Site_Name>Auto Mute - sound control software</NewsFeed_Site_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Site_URL>https://auto-mute.com</NewsFeed_Site_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Title>Auto Mute - software to make computer silent</NewsFeed_Title>
    <NewsFeed_Description_250>Small software utility to make PC silent when it's turning on or is
      waking up. The sound is automatically muted when the computer is turning off or is going to
      suspend mode. The next system start generates no sound even if you forgot to turn it off.</NewsFeed_Description_250>
    <NewsFeed_Description_70>Small software utility to make PC silent when it is turning on</NewsFeed_Description_70>
    <NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>This PAD extension allows you to add your RSS and Atom news feeds info
      into your PAD file. This info can be used by RSS feed submission software or by feed
      directories themselves.</NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>
  </NewsFeed>
  <Site>
    <Site_FORM>Y</Site_FORM>
    <Site_VERSION>1.0</Site_VERSION>
    <Site_URL>https://Submit-Everywhere.com/extensions/Site.htm</Site_URL>
    <Site_DESCRIPTION>This PAD extension allows you to add your site info into your PAD file. This
      info can be used by site submission software or by web directories themselves.</Site_DESCRIPTION>
    <Site_Contact_Email>pad@karpolan.com</Site_Contact_Email>
    <Site_Contact_First_Name>Anton</Site_Contact_First_Name>
    <Site_Site_Title>Auto Mute - software to make computer silent by default</Site_Site_Title>
    <Site_Site_URL>https://auto-mute.com</Site_Site_URL>
    <Site_Description_100>Small software utility to make PC silent when it is turning on or is
      waking up.</Site_Description_100>
    <Site_Description_250>Small software utility to make PC silent when it's turning on or is waking
      up. The sound is automatically muted when the computer is turning off or is going to suspend
      mode. The next system start generates no sound even if you forgot to turn it off.</Site_Description_250>
    <Site_Description_450>Small software utility to make PC silent when it's turning on or is waking
      up. The sound is automatically muted when the computer is turning off or is going to suspend
      mode. The next system start is absolutely silent even if you forgot to turn the sound off in
      previous session. After that you can enable sound effects manually, using a shortcut
      combination. Moreover, you may use this keyboard shortcut to quickly switch the sound on and
      off.</Site_Description_450>
    <Site_Keywords>mute sound, turn off sound, quiet logon, quiet logoff, quiet computer, quiet
      start, silent computer, silent logon, silent start</Site_Keywords>
    <Site_Contact_Last_Name>Karpenko</Site_Contact_Last_Name>
  </Site>
  <Program_Info>
    <Program_Name>Auto Mute</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>4.5</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>08</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>22</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2012</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>0.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>WinXP,WinVista,WinVista x64,Win7 x32,Win7
      x64,Win2000,WinServer,Win98,WinME,WinNT 4.x</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Added option to disable Internet features (updates, PingNotify statistics,
      etc.) Memory consumption improved.</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_System_Requirements>none</Program_System_Requirements>
    <Program_Category_Class>System Utilities::Automation Tools</Program_Category_Class>
    <File_Info>
      <File_Size_Bytes>565715</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>552</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>0.54</File_Size_MB>
      <Filename_Versioned></Filename_Versioned>
      <Filename_Previous></Filename_Previous>
      <Filename_Generic></Filename_Generic>
      <Filename_Long></Filename_Long>
    </File_Info>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Count></Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Other_Info></Expire_Other_Info>
      <Expire_Month></Expire_Month>
      <Expire_Day></Expire_Day>
      <Expire_Year></Expire_Year>
    </Expire_Info>
    <Program_Categories>Automation,Audio,Sound,Tools,System,Utilities,Software,Notebook,Computer</Program_Categories>
    <Limitations>none</Limitations>
    <Awards>Many awards from different download archives and review sites</Awards>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code></Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other></Program_Cost_Other>
    <Program_Specific_Category></Program_Specific_Category>
    <Includes_JAVA_VM></Includes_JAVA_VM>
    <Includes_VB_Runtime></Includes_VB_Runtime>
    <Includes_DirectX></Includes_DirectX>
  </Program_Info>
  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://auto-mute.com</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://auto-mute.com/download/</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://auto-mute.com/images/screenshot.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>https://auto-mute.com/images/icon-32x32.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>https://auto-mute.com/pad.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>https://auto-mute.com/files/auto-mute.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL>https://auto-mute.com/files/auto-mute.zip</Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1></Additional_Download_URL_1>
      <Additional_Download_URL_2></Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>
  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>This Software may be distributed freely through on-line services,
      bulletin boards, or other forms of electronic media, as long as the files are distributed in
      their entirety. Computer Magazines/Archives are authorized to distribute Software on any Cover
      Disk or CD-ROM without an individual permission.</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>This is the End User License Agreement (the "Agreement") is a legal agreement between you,
      the end-user ("Licensee"), and KARPOLAN, the manufacturer and the copyright owner ("Owner"),
      for the use of the "Auto Mute" aka "AutoMute" software product ("Software").

      By using this Software or storing this program on a computer drive (or other media), you are
      agreeing to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. If you do not agree with the terms of
      this Agreement, please remove this Software from your system.


      Rights
      ======

      The Software is protected by copyright laws and international copyright treaties, as well as
      other intellectual property laws and treaties. Software is licensed, not sold. Software is
      free to use and includes no technical support. The origin of this Software must not be
      misrepresented.


      Copyright
      =========

      All title, including but not limited to copyrights, in and to the Software and any copies
      thereof are owned by Owner or its suppliers. All title and intellectual property rights in and
      to the content which may be accessed through use of the Software is the property of the
      respective content owner and may be protected by applicable copyright or other intellectual
      property laws and treaties. This Agreement grants you no rights to use such content. All
      rights not expressly granted are reserved by Owner.


      Distribution
      ============

      This Software may be distributed freely through on-line services, bulletin boards, or other
      forms of electronic media, as long as the files are distributed in their entirety. Computer
      Magazines/Archives are authorized to distribute Software on any Cover Disk or CD-ROM without
      an individual permission.


      Restrictions
      ============

      You may not alter this Software in any way, including changing or removing any messages or
      windows. You may not decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble or otherwise reduce this
      Software to a human perceivable form. You may not modify, rent or resell this Software for
      profit, or create any derivative works, based upon this Software.


      Disclaimer
      ==========

      This Software is provided on an "as is" basis without warranty of any kind, expressed or
      implied, including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability and
      suitability for a particular purpose. The person using the Software bears all risk as to the
      quality and performance of the Software. Owner will not be liable for any special, incidental,
      consequential, indirect or similar damages due to loss of data or any other reason, even if
      Owner or an agent of Owner has been advised of the possibility of such damages. In no event
      will Owner be liable for costs of any damages. You acknowledge that you have read this
      license, understood it, and agreed to be bound by its terms.</EULA>
  </Permissions>
  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>mute sound, turn off sound, quiet logon, quiet logoff, quiet computer, quiet start,
        silent computer, silent logon, silent start</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Makes computer silent when it's turning on</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Small software utility to make PC silent when it is turning on or is waking up.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Small software utility to make PC silent when it's turning on or is waking up.
        The sound is automatically muted when the computer is turning off or is going to suspend
        mode. The next system start generates no sound even if you forgot to turn it off.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Small software utility to make PC silent when it's turning on or is waking up.
        The sound is automatically muted when the computer is turning off or is going to suspend
        mode. The next system start is absolutely silent even if you forgot to turn the sound off in
        previous session. After that you can enable sound effects manually, using a shortcut
        combination. Moreover, you may use this keyboard shortcut to quickly switch the sound on and
        off.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Has your child ever been awakened with the loud "Ta-Dam!" sound your laptop
        played when you opened it at late evening? Did you ever open notebook on conference and the
        computer loudly notifies you about new messages or something? I bet, you wanted to smash the
        computer into smithereens then. Each time this happens to me, I promise myself to disable
        the sound before logging off, but I always forget about this in few minutes.

        So I've created small software utility to make PC silent when it's turning on or is waking
        up. Solution is very easy! The sound is automatically muted when the computer is turning off
        or is going to suspend mode. The next system start is absolutely silent even if you forgot
        to turn the sound off in previous session. After that you can enable sound effects manually,
        using a shortcut combination. Moreover, you may use this keyboard shortcut to quickly switch
        the sound on and off.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
    <Russian>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Ваш ребенок никогда не просыпался от громкого звука "Та-дам!", который выдавал
        ваш ноутбук, когда вы открывали его поздним вечером? А было такое что на конференциях или
        других публичных местах, компьютер громко уведомляет всех присутствующих о новых сообщениях
        или издавал другие громкие звуки? Бьюсь об заклад, что в такие моменты вы были готовы
        разбить компьютер вдребезги и пополам. Каждый раз, когда такое происходило со мной, я
        клятвенно обещал себе, что обязательно отключу звук до выхода из системы, но я всякий раз
        забывал об этом буквально за несколько минут.

        Я долго мучился, но потом решил создать небольшую программку, которая автоматически
        заглушает звук при выключении компьютера или перехода ноутбука в спящий режим. Таким
        образом, последующее включение компьютера, пробуждение или вход пользователя в систему
        становится абсолютно беззвучным! Позже, есть возможность включить звуковые эффекты вручную,
        используя определенную комбинацию клавиш. Так же это сочетание клавиш можно использовать для
        быстрого включении и выключения звука во время работы.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Ваш ребенок никогда не просыпался от громкого звука "Та-дам!", который выдавал
        ваш ноутбук, когда вы открывали его поздним вечером? А было такое что на конференциях или
        других публичных местах, компьютер громко уведомляет всех присутствующих о новых сообщениях
        или издавал другие громкие звуки? Бьюсь об заклад, что в такие моменты вы были готовы
        разбить компьютер вдребезги и пополам. Программа Auto Mute - отличное решение это проблемы.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Ваш ребенок никогда не просыпался от громкого звука "Та-дам!", который выдавал
        ваш ноутбук, когда вы открывали его поздним вечером? А было такое что на конференциях или
        других публичных местах, компьютер громко выдает звуковое сообщение?</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Решение проблемы громкого поведения компьютера в тихих местах</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Компьютер больше не издает громких звуков</Char_Desc_45>
      <Keywords>звук, музыка, громко, тихо, отключить звук, приглушить звук, беззвучный</Keywords>
    </Russian>
    <German>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Hat Ihr Kind jemals mit dem lauten "Ta-Dam geweckt!" Sound Ihren Laptop
        gespielt, wenn Sie sie geöffnet am späten Abend? Haben Sie schon einmal geöffnet Notebook
        auf die Konferenz und der Computer meldet laut, Sie über neue Nachrichten oder was? Ich
        wette, Sie wollten den Computer in Scherben dann zu zerschlagen. Jedes Mal, wenn mir das
        passiert, das verspreche ich mir den Klang vor der Abmeldung zu deaktivieren, aber ich habe
        immer über diese vergessen in wenigen Minuten.

        Deshalb habe ich kleines Software-Programm geschaffen, um PC schweigen, wenn es auf Drehen
        oder Aufwachen. Lösung ist ganz einfach! Der Ton wird automatisch stumm geschaltet, wenn der
        Computer ausgeschaltet ist oder sich drehen wird, um Modus anzuhalten. Die nächsten
        System-Start ist ganz still, auch wenn Sie vergessen haben, den Ton ausschalten in den
        vorangegangenen Sitzung. Danach können Sie manuell aktivieren Soundeffekte, über eine
        Verknüpfung Kombination. Darüber hinaus können Sie diese Tastenkombination verwenden, um
        schnell den Ton ein-und ausschalten.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Kleine Software-Dienstprogramm, um PC schweigen, wenn es auf Drehen oder
        Aufwachen. Der Ton wird automatisch stumm geschaltet, wenn der Computer ausgeschaltet ist
        oder sich drehen wird, um Modus anzuhalten. Die nächsten System-Start ist ganz still, auch
        wenn Sie vergessen haben, den Ton ausschalten in den vorangegangenen Sitzung. Danach können
        Sie manuell aktivieren Soundeffekte, über eine Verknüpfung Kombination.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Kleine Software-Dienstprogramm, um PC schweigen, wenn es auf Drehen oder
        Aufwachen. Der Ton wird automatisch stumm geschaltet, wenn der Computer ausgeschaltet ist
        oder sich drehen wird, um Modus anzuhalten.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Kleine Software, um PC schweigen, wenn es auf Drehen oder Aufwachen</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Macht PC schweigen, wenn es drehen auf</Char_Desc_45>
      <Keywords>schweigen, sound, stumm geschaltet</Keywords>
    </German>
    <French>
      <Keywords>silencieux, sonores</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Donne PC silencieux quand il tourne sur</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Petit utilitaire pour faire le PC silencieux quand il tourne sur ou se réveille.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Votre enfant a déjà été réveillée par le haut "Ta-Dam! son de votre ordinateur
        portable joué quand vous l'avez ouvert le soir tard? Saviez-vous portable toujours ouvert
        sur la conférence et l'ordinateur signale fort qu'on sujet de nouveaux messages?</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Votre enfant a déjà été réveillée par le haut "Ta-Dam! son de votre ordinateur
        portable joué quand vous l'avez ouvert le soir tard? Saviez-vous portable toujours ouvert
        sur la conférence et l'ordinateur signale fort qu'on sujet de nouveaux messages ou quoi? Je
        parie que vous avez voulu briser l'ordinateur en éclats alors.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Votre enfant a déjà été réveillée par le haut "Ta-Dam! son de votre ordinateur
        portable joué quand vous l'avez ouvert le soir tard? Saviez-vous portable toujours ouvert
        sur la conférence et l'ordinateur signale fort qu'on sujet de nouveaux messages ou quoi? Je
        parie que vous avez voulu briser l'ordinateur en éclats alors. Chaque fois que cela
        m'arrive, je me promets de désactiver le son avant de vous déconnecter, mais je l'oublie
        toujours à ce sujet dans quelques minutes.

        J'ai donc créé utilitaire petit logiciel pour faire le PC silencieux quand il tourne sur ou
        se réveille. Solution est très facile! Le son est automatiquement coupé lorsque l'ordinateur
        est d'éteindre ou va suspendre mode. Le prochain démarrage du système est absolument
        silencieux, même si vous avez oublié de mettre le son en session précédente. Après cela,
        vous pouvez activer les effets sonores manuellement, en utilisant une combinaison de
        raccourcis. En outre, vous mai utiliser ce raccourci clavier pour passer rapidement le son
        ou le désactiver.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </French>
    <Spanish>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Su hijo ha sido despertado con el fuerte "Ta-Dam!" de sonido de su computadora
        portátil cuando se jugó la abrió al final de la tarde? ¿Te cuaderno siempre abierta sobre la
        conferencia y el equipo en voz alta le notifica sobre nuevos mensajes o algo así? Apuesto a
        que usted quería romper en mil pedazos el equipo entonces. Cada vez que esto me pasa a mí,
        me prometo a mí mismo para desactivar el sonido antes de cerrar la sesión, pero siempre me
        olvido de eso, en pocos minutos.

        Así que he creado pequeños programas informáticos de utilidad para hacer PC silencioso
        cuando está encendido o se está despertando. La solución es muy fácil! El sonido se silencia
        automáticamente cuando el ordenador está apagado o se va a modo de suspensión. El próximo
        reinicio del sistema es totalmente silencioso, incluso si usted se olvidó de apagar el
        sonido en la sesión anterior. Después de que se pueden habilitar efectos de sonido
        manualmente, utilizando una combinación de acceso directo. Además, usted puede usar este
        método abreviado de teclado para cambiar rápidamente el sonido encendido y apagado.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Su hijo ha sido despertado con el fuerte "Ta-Dam!" de sonido de su computadora
        portátil cuando se jugó la abrió al final de la tarde? ¿Te cuaderno siempre abierta sobre la
        conferencia y el equipo en voz alta le notifica sobre nuevos mensajes o algo así? Apuesto a
        que usted quería romper en mil pedazos el equipo entonces. Cada vez que esto me pasa a mí,
        me prometo a mí mismo para desactivar el sonido antes de cerrar la sesión...</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Su hijo ha sido despertado con el fuerte "Ta-Dam!" de sonido de su computadora
        portátil cuando se jugó la abrió al final de la tarde? ¿Te cuaderno siempre abierta sobre la
        conferencia y el equipo en voz alta le notifica sobre nuevos mensajes?</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_45>PC hace en silencio cuando se inicia</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Utilidad pequeña para que PC en silencio cuando se encienda o se está despertand</Char_Desc_80>
      <Keywords>silencio, mudo</Keywords>
    </Spanish>
    <Italian>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Il vostro bambino mai stato svegliato con la forte "Ta-Dam!" suono il vostro
        computer portatile riprodotto quando si aprì la sera tardi? Avete mai aperto sul taccuino
        conferenza e il computer ti avvisa ad alta voce sui nuovi messaggi o qualcosa del genere?
        Scommetto, avete voluto distruggere il computer in frantumi allora. Ogni volta che questo
        succede a me, prometto a me stesso di disabilitare il suono prima della disconnessione, ma
        mi dimentico sempre di questo in pochi minuti.

        Così ho creato piccola utility software per PC in silenzio quando è acceso o si sta
        svegliando. Soluzione è molto facile! Il suono viene automaticamente disattivato quando il
        computer è spento o sta per modalità di sospensione. Il prossimo avvio del sistema è
        assolutamente silenzioso anche se si è dimenticato di disattivare il suono in sessione
        precedente. Dopo di che è possibile abilitare gli effetti sonori manualmente, utilizzando
        una combinazione di scelta rapida. Inoltre, è possibile utilizzare questa scorciatoia da
        tastiera per passare rapidamente l'audio on e off.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Un piccolo software di utilità per rendere PC silenzioso quando è acceso o si
        sta svegliando. Il suono viene automaticamente disattivato quando il computer è spento o sta
        per modalità di sospensione. Il prossimo avvio del sistema è assolutamente silenzioso anche
        se si è dimenticato di disattivare il suono in sessione precedente. Dopo di che è possibile
        abilitare gli effetti sonori manualmente, utilizzando una combinazione di scelta rapida.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Software PC per fare silenzio quando è acceso o si sta svegliando. Il suono
        viene automaticamente disattivato quando il computer è spento o sta per modalità di
        sospensione. L'avvio del sistema prossima genera alcun suono.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Software PC per fare in silenzio quando si accende o si sta svegliando.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Rende computer silenzioso quando è acceso</Char_Desc_45>
      <Keywords>suono muto, disattivare il suono, tranquillo accesso, disconnessione tranquilla,
        tranquilla computer, avviare tranquilla, silenziosa computer, accesso silenzioso, muto
        inizio</Keywords>
    </Italian>
    <Portuguese>
      <Keywords>mudo, desligue logon, som calmo, tranquilo logoff, o computador quieto, tímido
        início, computador silencioso, logon, Silent início</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_2000>O seu filho já foi acordado com o alto "Ta-Dam!" o som do seu laptop jogado
        quando você o abriu na tarde da noite? Você notebook sempre aberta, em conferências e em voz
        alta o computador avisa sobre novas mensagens ou algo assim? Aposto que você queria destruir
        o computador em pedacinhos depois. Cada vez que isso acontece comigo, eu prometo a mim mesma
        para desativar o som antes de fazer logoff, mas eu sempre esquecer isso em poucos minutos.
        Então eu criei utilitário pequeno para fazer silêncio quando PC é ligar ou está acordando.
        Solução é muito fácil! O som é silenciado automaticamente quando o computador está desligado
        ou está indo para o modo de suspensão. O início do sistema seguinte é absolutamente
        silencioso, mesmo se você se esqueceu de desligar o som na sessão anterior. Depois disso,
        você pode ativar efeitos sonoros manualmente, usando uma combinação de atalho. Além disso,
        você pode usar esse atalho para alternar rapidamente o som ligado e desligado.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Char_Desc_450>Software PC para fazer silêncio quando ela ligar. O som é silenciado
        automaticamente quando o computador está desligado ou está indo para o modo de suspensão. O
        início do sistema seguinte é absolutamente silencioso, mesmo se você se esqueceu de desligar
        o som na sessão anterior. Depois disso, você pode ativar efeitos sonoros manualmente, usando
        um atalho. Você pode usar esse atalho para alternar rapidamente o som ligado e desligado.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_250>Software PC para fazer silêncio quando ela ligar. O som é silenciado
        automaticamente quando o computador está desligado ou está indo para o modo de suspensão. O
        início do sistema seguinte é absolutamente silencioso.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_80>Pequeno software para tornar o PC silencioso quando se ligar ou está acordando.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_45>Computador faz silêncio quando está girando e</Char_Desc_45>
    </Portuguese>
  </Program_Descriptions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>